Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records - Addendum E
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Programs and Colleges, Series IV
  - Thailand
    - Payap University: Project Reports, 1989-1994 (Box 25, Folder 307)
    - Payap University: Proposals, Grants, Etc., 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 308)
    - Mahidol University: General, 1990-1996 (Box 25, Folder 309)
  - Vietnam
    - College of Foreign Languages, Vietnam National University, 1992-1997 (Box 25, Folder 310)